

Muflihun Azis, S.Tr.T

Data Center & System Operation (DCSO) - IT Specialist

+62 852-1380-6325

muflihunazis123@gmail.com

muflihunazisportofolio.vercel.app

https://www.linkedin.com/in/muflihun-azis

Fresh graduate of Applied Bachelor of Computer and Network Engineering, Department of Informatics & Computer Engineering, Ujung Pandang State of Polytechnic and my current position as Data Center & System Operation at PT eBdesk Teknologi. Experienced and skilled in designing, prototyping, & creating websites and IT Infrastructure & Networking Specialist. GPA score is 3.54/4.00 (Cumlaude) & TOEFL Score is 423

Experience -

Data Center & System Operations (DSCO)

PT eBdesk Teknologi (Full-Time) December 2024 - now

IT Infrastructure Officer

Hotel Horison Ultima Makassar (Full-Time) September 2024 - November 2024

Technical Support

Internship Remoted at GAOTek Inc. Sep 2023 - March 2024

IT Support & Infrastructure

Internship at KPPBC TMP B MAKASSAR August 2023 - Dec 2023 Responsible for the task are server monitoring, daily checking & reporting, Data Center Infrastructure, Virtualization, Architecture, Management, Construction and Relocation. Aside from that, about Linux Server, Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL), System & Network Monitoring Tools, Internet Troubleshooting, LAN-WAN, Software Troubleshooting, IT Hardware Support, IT Audit, IT Infrastructure Operations, IT Controls, Mikrotik & Cisco Networking, Computer System Desain & Maintenance

Responsible for the task are IT Controls, Information Technology Infrastructure, Software & Internet Troubleshooting, Computer System Design, Software Support, Software as a Service (SaaS), Computer Systems Maintenance, Server & CCTV Monitoring, Internet Security, Computer Consultation, Analytical Skills, Problem Solving skills, Internet & Software Installation

Tech Support Position at Remote Internship by GAOTek Inc has jobdesc are content sourcing & uploading, source relevant technical content, FAQs & troubleshooting tips, format and organize content on our based website. Upload and publish content & ensuring proper categorization.

IT Support & Infrastructure at Internship KPPBC TMP B Makassar has jobdesc are responsible for the availability of IT infrastructure development, Monitoring & maintenance server hardware or software, networks, power systems & cables. Mastering Switching, routing, firewalls, LAN/WLANS, VPNs & VoIP & TCP/IP

Education

Applied Bachelor of Computer and Network Engineering

Ujung Pandang State of Polytechnic Graduated: August 2024

Computer and Network Engineering SMKN 1 SINJAI

Graduated: July 2020

Skills -

- Data Center Operation
- Full Stack Web Development
- Android Development
- IT Networking & IT Infrastructure
- Switching, Routing, VPNs & VoIP
- System Architecture Operation
- IT Troubleshooting & Audit
- Mikrotik & Cisco Networking
- Linux Server Monitoring
- Server Management & Virtualization

The study program is accredited Excellent (A) & be an Awardee of the Unggulan Scholarship from KEMDIKBUDRISTEK RI, actively involved activity in HME-PNUP as Chair of the Class Representative Council (DPK). Another that, actively participates in scientific research activities in the field of cyber security and routinely participates in Community Service activities and scholarship socialization on campus

Became a Top 10 Finalist in the APJII Mikrotik Network Olympiad, actively involved in OSIS activities as Deputy Chairperson of OSIS. In addition, it succeeded in becoming 3rd place in the Computer Engineering and Network Department of SMKN 1 SINJAI

Certification

- Certification of Competence and Profession for Vocational Students By PNUP
- Fullstack Web Development Using Laravel & Tailwind CSS By KEMNAKER RI
- Junior Web Developer Competency By VSGA KOMINFO RI
- Junior Web Developer Training By VSGA KOMINFO RI
- Dicoding Developer Coaching By Dicoding Indonesia
- IoT Summit 2022 By Indobot Academy
- Certification of Speakers for Talkshow Scholarship By BU INDOTIM
- Certified Internship IT Support & Infrastructure By KPPBC TMP B Makassar
- Certified Internship Tech Support By GAOTek Inc